http://www.poth-hille.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Main Menu
HomeProductsBeeswaxCandelilla WaxCarnauba WaxCeresine / Ozokerite WaxDepilatory WaxHista-FlexMicrocrystalline WaxMontan WaxNatural Wax BlendsParaffin WaxRapeseed WaxRefined Sumac WaxRice Bran WaxSoy WaxSpecialised WaxesSunflower WaxSurfboard WaxTissue Embedding WaxMore Products CloseServicesPrivate Label Candles and DiffusersOwn Label Surf Wax, Ski Wax and Curb WaxEve Victoria Home FragrancePrivate Label Histology Service CloseApplicationsCandlemaking WaxCoatingsCosmeticsDepilatory WaxHistologyIndustrial WaxesPharmaceutical & Personal CarePolishesSpecialised CloseAbout UsNews & BlogOur Location & Contact
Home
Mobile MenuHome
Products
Beeswax
Candelilla Wax
Carnauba Wax
Ceresine / Ozokerite Wax
Depilatory Wax
The Policy
This privacy policy notice is for this website; www.poth-hille.co.uk and served by Poth Hille and governs the privacy of those who use it. The purpose of this policy is to explain to you how we control, process, handle and protect your personal information while browsing or using this website, including your rights under current laws and regulations. If you do not agree to the following policy you may wish to cease viewing / using this website.
Policy key definitions:
“I”, “our”, “us”, or “we” refer to the business, Poth Hille.
“you”, “the user” refer to the person(s) using this website.
GDPR means General Data Protection Act.
PECR means Privacy & Electronic Communications Regulation.
ICO means Information Commissioner’s Office.
Cookies mean small files stored on a users computer or device.
Processing of your personal data
Under the GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation) we control and / or process any personal information about you electronically using the following lawful bases.
We are exempt from registration in the ICO Data Protection Register because we only processing personal data for the core business purposes.
Information that you voluntarily provide
We do not collect personally-identifiable information unless you choose to provide it to us. If you provide us with personally identifiable information, for example by sending an e-mail or by filling out a contact form and submitting it through our website, we use that information only to respond to your message and to help us provide you with the information and services that you request.
Retention of Information
We destroy the information we collect when the purpose for which it was provided has been fulfilled unless we are required to keep it longer by statute or official policy.
We do not store any personal data unless we have your prior permission, all data is stored securely. Unfortunately the sending of information via the internet is not totally secure and on occasion such information can be intercepted. We cannot guarantee the security of data that you choose to send us electronically, Sending such information is entirely at your own risk.
Sharing your Information
We do not share your information with third parties.
We will not disclose your personal information to any other party other than in accordance with this Privacy Policy and in the circumstances detailed below:
i. In the event that we sell any or all of our business to the buyer.
ii. Where we are legally required by law to disclose your personal information.
iii. To further fraud protection and reduce the risk of fraud.
Links to other sites
This site may have links to other websites. These may be links to private organisations, with their permission. Once you go to another site, you are subject to the privacy policy of the new site. It is always a good idea to read the Privacy Policy of any website that you visit.
Information Protection
For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, this computer system employs software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorised attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. If such monitoring reveals evidence of possible abuse or criminal activity, such evidence may be provided to appropriate law enforcement officials.
Your individual rights
Under the GDPR your rights are as follows. You can read more about your rights in details here;
the right to be informed;
the right of access;
the right to rectification;
the right to erasure;
the right to restrict processing;
the right to data portability;
the right to object; and
the right not to be subject to automated decision-making including profiling.
You also have the right to complain to the ICO [www.ico.org.uk] if you feel there is a problem with the way we are handling your data.
We handle subject access requests in accordance with the GDPR.
Internet Cookies
Our website uses cookies.
We will ask you to consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy when you visit our website. In using our website and agreeing to this policy you are consenting to the use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.
Here is how we handle information about your visit to our website.
We automatically collect and store information like the following concerning your visit.
-The Internet domain (for example, “xcompany.com” if you use a private Internet access account, or “yourschool.edu” if you connect from a university’s domain);
-Your IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access our website;
-The type of browser and operating system used to access our site;
-The date and time you access our site;
-The pages you visit; and
-If you linked to our website from another website, the address of that website.
We use this information to help us make our site more useful to visitors—to learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology our visitors use.
N.B. This is the standard information that is available to all website owners via their webserver logs.
Cookies
“Cookies” are small bits of text that are either used for the duration of a session (“session cookies”), or saved on a user’s hard drive in order to identify that user, or information about that user, the next time the user logs on to a website (“persistent cookies”).
A session cookie will expire at the end of the user session when the web browser is closed. A persistent cookie will remain valid until its set expiry date.
We use both session cookies and persistent cookies on this website.
We will send to you the following cookies:
Google Analytics – (_utma _utmb _utmc and _utmz). These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use this site.
Wordfence – (wordfence_verifiedHuman). This cookie is used by a third party security plugin called Wordfence. This cookie is used as a security feature to check whether the user of the website is human.
Email marketing messages & subscription
Under the GDPR we use the consent lawful basis for anyone subscribing to our newsletter or marketing mailing list. We only collect certain data about you, as detailed in the “Processing of your personal date” above. Any email marketing messages we send are done so through an EMS, email marketing service provider. An EMS is a third party service provider of software / applications that allows marketers to send out email marketing campaigns to a list of users.
Email marketing messages that we send may contain tracking beacons / tracked clickable links or similar server technologies in order to track subscriber activity within email marketing messages. Where used, such marketing messages may record a range of data such as; times, dates, I.P addresses, opens, clicks, forwards, geographic and demographic data. Such data, within its limitations will show the activity each subscriber made for that email campaign.
Any email marketing messages we send are in accordance with the GDPR and the PECR. We provide you with an easy method to withdraw your consent (unsubscribe) or manage your preferences / the information we hold about you at any time. See any marketing messages for instructions on how to unsubscribe or manage your preferences, you can also unsubscribe from all MailChimp lists, by following this link, otherwise contact the EMS provider.
Our EMS provider is; MailChimp. We hold the following information about you within our EMS system;
Email address
I.P address
Subscription time & date
Complaints and Further Information
If you need to contact us in relation with any concerns, complaints or any aspect of the use of this website and associated websites please contact us via e-mail: info@poth-hille.co.uk
Poth Hille & Co Ltd
Unit 18 Easter Industrial Park,
Ferry Lane South,
Rainham,
Essex,
RM13 9BP,
Tel: +44 (0)1708 526 828
Fax: +44(0)1708 525 695
Email: info@poth-hille.co.uk
© 2020 Poth Hille. All Rights Reserved.
Terms & Condiitions | Privacy Policy | Designed by Blitz Media
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.OkRead more
